http://www.cronin-co.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Cronin and Company LLC uses the information collected, including personally identifiable information, for a variety of purposes. For example, we use your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better products and services, respond to your inquiries or requests, communicate with you, update you on products, services or benefits, alert you to promotional offers, personalize the Site for you, contact you for market research, provide you with marketing information, newsletters or other information we think would be of particular interest. We will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such materials.
Cronin and Company LLC may also share your personally identifiable information and/or aggregate information with our affiliates, technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who create or maintain the Site, enhance its functionality or provide associated services. Please note that we reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information to our successors in business and purchasers (in whole or in part) of the Site’s assets.
Privacy Policy Changes/ Effective Date
This Policy was last changed on June 16, 2004. If Cronin and Company LLC makes changes to this Policy, it will be revised so that you always know what information we currently gather, how we might use that information and to whom we may disclose it. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time and without notice and any such changes immediately take effect when posted unless we advise you otherwise. Your continued use of the Services and/or the Site after this Policy has been amended shall constitute your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Policy, as amended.
